<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kine&#39;s info</title>
    <link>https://blog.kine.cz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kine&#39;s info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.kine.cz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unattended access to local resources - WCF Relay</title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/localfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/localfs/</guid>
      <description>In many cases you need to work with resources (files, scales, card readers etc.), which are available on local network/PC, from within Microsoft Dynamics 365 Business Central which runs somewhere in the Cloud. I will show you one way how to solve these things.
What is the problem? Different processes in Business Central can need some local resources of yours. In a simples case it could be some file on your disk on your PC (or server on local network).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshot debugger on OnPrem - what you need to know to set it up</title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/snapshotdebuggeronprem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/snapshotdebuggeronprem/</guid>
      <description>When you want to use Snapshot Debugging on your OnPrem environment, may be you can hit this error when trying to initialize it:
Error: The SSL connection could not be established, see inner exception.... In some cirumstances you can even have problem to start the BC Service when you enable the Snapshot Debugger endpoint.
What is the problem? For standard endpoint, which we are using for longer time already, like client endpoint (default port 7046), OData (7048) and Dev (7049), the Management console for BC Server is automatically setting some things in background when you save the settings in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture of PTE - Split or not to Split?</title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/ptearchitecture1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 16:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/ptearchitecture1/</guid>
      <description>On Directions EMEA in Milan I delivered session about Architecture of PTE for Business Central. I was trying to find some rules when or why you should or shouldn&amp;rsquo;t split your PTE into multiple apps. Now I will try to catch this into this article.
Split or not to split Some partners are putting everything into one app per customer. Some are splitting all to separate apps based on different rules like per process, per area etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/newblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 10:00:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/newblog/</guid>
      <description>New blog May be you already noticed that my original blog on dynamicsusers.net (original URL was https://www.dynamicsuser.net/nav/b/kine) is gone. I am building new one from scratch. May be it is time to begin something new and cut off the Dynamics NAV history.
Because todays it is easy to use GitHub as a platform for the blog (and thus using git and vscode to &amp;ldquo;post&amp;rdquo; the articles), I decided to use HUGO as the framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/about/</guid>
      <description>About me I have more than 35 years of experience with software development and IT in general. In the year 2001, after finishing university, I joined the NAV world in NAVERTICA company as NAV developer. Having a wide area of knowledge in programming languages and connected areas is helping me to understand “how it works” and is giving me background for solving different tasks. For the last years, I am working more with GIT, Powershell, and Azure DevOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you need professional services from me, contact NAVERTICA a.s. sales. I am employee in the company and I am not able to serve you directly.
If you want to support me personally, you can use the BuyMeCoffee tipping system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
