<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kine&#39;s info</title>
    <link>https://blog.kine.cz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kine&#39;s info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 16:51:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.kine.cz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Architecture of PTE - Split or not to Split?</title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/ptearchitecture1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 16:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/ptearchitecture1/</guid>
      <description>On Directions EMEA in Milan I delivered session about Architecture of PTE for Business Central. I was trying to find some rules when or why you should or shouldn&amp;rsquo;t split your PTE into multiple apps. Now I will try to catch this into this article.
Split or not to split Some partners are putting everything into one app per customer. Some are splitting all to separate apps based on different rules like per process, per area etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/newblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 10:00:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/posts/newblog/</guid>
      <description>New blog May be you already noticed that my original blog on dynamicsusers.net (original URL was https://www.dynamicsuser.net/nav/b/kine) is gone. I am building new one from scratch. May be it is time to begin something new and cut off the Dynamics NAV history.
Because todays it is easy to use GitHub as a platform for the blog (and thus using git and vscode to &amp;ldquo;post&amp;rdquo; the articles), I decided to use HUGO as the framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/about/</guid>
      <description>About me I have more than 35 years of experience with software development and IT in general. In the year 2001, after finishing university, I joined the NAV world in NAVERTICA company as NAV developer. Having a wide area of knowledge in programming languages and connected areas is helping me to understand “how it works” and is giving me background for solving different tasks. For the last years, I am working more with GIT, Powershell, and Azure DevOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blog.kine.cz/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kine.cz/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you need professional services from me, contact NAVERTICA a.s. sales. I am employee in the company and I am not able to serve you directly.
If you want to support me personally, you can use the BuyMeCoffee tipping system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
